They have arrived.
Proximity is a science fiction, drama film directed by Eric Demeusy.
A young NASA JPL scientist is abducted by extraterrestrials but when no one believes his story he
becomes obsessed with finding proof which leads him on a journey of discovery.
Isaac, played by Ryan Masson.
Sara, played by Highdee Kuan.
Zed, played by Christian Prentice.
Agent Graves, played by Shaw Jones.
Girlfriend, played by Nomi Abadi.
Carl Meissner, played by Don Scribner.
Proximity is a 2020 American science fiction drama film written and
directed by Eric Demeusy in his directorial debut.
The film stars Ryan Masson, Highdee Kuan, Christian Prentice, and Shaw Jones.
Proximity was released on demand on May 15, 2020, and
received poor reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of nasa, secret government
organization, extraterrestrial, scientist, tracking device.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.